Can you remember what you ate yesterday?
你还记得自己昨天吃了什么吗？
If asked, most people will be able to give a vague description of their main meals: breakfast, lunch, dinner.
要是有人问起，大多数人都能含糊地描述一下自己的几顿正餐：早餐、午餐、晚餐。
But can you be sure you’ve noted every snack bar in your car, or every handful of nuts at your desk?
但你能确定自己记下了在车里吃的每一根零食棒，或是在办公桌前吃的每一把坚果吗？
Most people will have a feeling that they’ve missed something out.
大多数人都会感觉自己漏掉了些什么。
We originally had this suspicion back in 2016, puzzled by the fact that national statistics showed calorie consumption falling dramatically over past decades.
我们最初产生这种怀疑，还是早在2016年，当时国家统计数据显示，过去几十年间热量摄入量大幅下降，这一事实令我们困惑不解。
We found reliable evidence that people were drastically under-reporting what they ate.
我们找到了可靠的证据，表明人们一直在大幅少报自己吃的东西。
Now the Office for National Statistics has confirmed that we are consuming 50% more calories than our national statistics claim.
如今，国家统计局已经证实，我们摄入的热量比国家统计数据所称的多50%。
Why is this happening?
为什么会出现这种情况？
We can point to at least three potential causes.
我们可以指出至少三个可能的原因。
One is the rise in obesity levels itself.
其一是肥胖水平本身在上升。
Under-reporting rates are much higher for obese people, because they simply consume more food, and thus have more to remember.
肥胖者的少报率要高得多，原因很简单：他们吃的食物更多，因而要记住的也更多。
Another cause is that the proportion of people who are trying to lose weight has been increasing over time.
另一个原因是，试图减肥的人所占的比例随着时间的推移一直在上升。
People who want to lose weight are more likely to under-report their eating—regardless of whether they are overweight or not.
想减肥的人更有可能少报自己吃的东西，无论他们是否超重。
This may be driven partly by self-deception or “wishful thinking”.
这可能在一定程度上源于自我欺骗或“一厢情愿的想法”。
The final potential cause is an increase in snacking and eating out over recent decades—both in terms of how often they happen and how much they contribute to our overall energy intake.
最后一个可能的原因是，近几十年来，吃零食和在外就餐的情况增多了——既体现在频率上，也体现在它们占我们总能量摄入的比重上。
Again, there is evidence that food consumed out of the home is one of the most poorly recorded categories in surveys.
同样，有证据表明，在外面吃的食物是调查中记录得最差的类别之一。
So, what’s the message conveyed?
那么，这传达出什么信息呢？
For statistics, we should invest in more accurate measurement options.
在统计方面，我们应该投资于更准确的测量方案。
For policy, we need to focus on options that make it easy for people to eat fewer calories.
在政策方面，我们需要把重点放在那些能让人们轻松少摄入热量的方案上。
If people do not know how much they are eating, it can be really hard for them to stick to a diet.
如果人们不清楚自己吃了多少，就可能真的很难坚持节食。
Also, we should be looking for new ways to ensure what people eat won’t have much impact on their waistlines.
此外，我们应该寻找新办法，确保人们吃的东西不会对腰围产生太大影响。
If this works, it won’t matter if they can’t remember what they ate yesterday.
如果这能奏效，那么即便人们记不起自己昨天吃了什么，也无关紧要了。